

Carlos Soria Labrandero Videogame Programmer

programcocodev@gmail.com

Portfolio

<u>Linkedin</u>

About me

I am a proactive person and passionate about the world of video games. I keep abreast of the latest developments in the industry.

My greatest ambition is to create amazing and unique experiences. I am passionate about game mechanics, gameplay and artificial intelligence. When I have some free time, I research procedural generation, NPC behaviour and game flow for gameplay, especially in combat, to make it harmonious and interesting. Also, creating a good visual environment and giving visual feedback with VFX.

Experience

Lucky Dodo

09/2021 - 07/2022

I had the pleasure of working with a great team on **Seeking Light**. I was responsible for the AI in the early stages and later the game flow, save systems, level streaming, UI and VFX. The game is published on Steam and won the GDWC 2022 Hobby Category Award and other mentions. Link: <u>Seeking Light - Steam</u>

Creek Games

10/2022 - 03/2023

I joined the **Fragments of Child** project as a collaborator, programming various gameplay and puzzle tasks. Later, together with another colleague, a custom artificial intelligence system was designed and implemented to run on the Unreal Engine. The teaser for the first versions of the game can be found here: <u>Foundry Teaser</u> You can also check out his <u>Linkedin</u> page to see some of the awards he won during the development process.

Experience

Ardis Software S.L.

02/2023 - Current

Project to develop a **3D editing tool** in the cloud. They are dedicated to the sale of specialised software in the optimisation of wood cutting. I am programming several tools so that you can design all kinds of furniture and other elements. They are also connected to the API of the optimisation programs to automate the manufacturing process.

3VE 06/2018 - 01/2019

I made infographics of buildings for architectural projects and I also developed a programme in Unity where I was responsible for adding functionality to the UI.

Competences

- C/C++, C#, Python, GLSL, Typecript, Lua
- SFML, SDL, SQLite, OpenGL, GLM, OpenAL
- Unity, Unreal Engine 4/5
- Angular, React, Node.js

Academic background

ESAT

HND In Computing

Progresa

3D animation, video games and interactive environments

Languages

- Spanish Native
- English Advanced